-=破烂熊字幕组=-
校对&时间轴: 小魉
~ 母亲 ~
~ Mater~
~ 眼泪 ~
~ Lacrimarum ~
~ 眼泪之母 ~
~ Mater Lacrimarum ~
母亲
Mater.
啊哈 啊哈 慢点
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Easy now.
你没事吧?      嗨 这下面有东西!
You okay?        Hey, there's something down here!
"奥斯卡・德拉瓦莱 卒于1815年"
"Oscar de la Valle, 1815.''
斩断铁链
Cut the chains.
今天晚上我们会把他重新埋葬在...
We'll rebury him on the other side of the cemetery...
公墓的另一边
later tonight.
那骨灰瓮呢?
And the urn?
放在我车上
Put it in my car.
等一下 主教
Hang on, Monsignor.
亲爱的迈克尔...
Dear Michael...
今天我们找到了一样令我恐惧的东西...
we found something alarming today...
就在公墓的外面
right outside of the cemetery.
我现在把这个骨灰瓮寄给你...
I'm sending this urn over to you...
请你检查它里面的东西
that you can examine its contents.
你比我更了解巫术的历史...
You know more about the history of magic...
和秘传学问
and esoteric sciences than I do...
我希望你能解除...
and I'm hoping you can deny...
我的忧虑
what I fear.
罗马 古代艺术博物馆
萨拉 你见到迈克尔了吗?
Hey, Sarah. You seen Michael?
有几个小时没见着了
Not for a couple of hours.
他带保罗去看病了      噢 没错
He had to take Paul to the doctor.        Oh, that's right.
我在想他为什么不接电话
I was wondering why he wasn't answering his cell.
过来看样东西
Come take a look at something.
什么?
What?
过来 我带你去看 跟我走
Here, let me show you. Come with me.
好吧
All right.
是什么?      过来 我告诉你
What is it?        Come. I'll show you.
我知道不早了 但你真该看看它
I know it's late, but you really need to check this out.
真的      嗯
Really?        Yeah.
别吊我胃口 到底是什么?
Don't keep me hanging. What is it?
好的 是一个骨灰瓮      真的?
All right. It's an urn.        Really?
嗯
Yes.
哪儿来的?      维泰博(意大利城市)
Where'd it come from?        Viterbo.
布鲁斯卡主教寄过来的
A Monsignor Brusca sent it.
他们在一具1815年入土的棺木上发现它的
They found it with a coffin buried in 1815.
母亲
Mater.
真是奇妙!      我从未见过这种东西
Isn't this amazing?        I've never seen anything like this.
我知道
I know.
迈克尔的电话还是打不通
Oh. Michael's phone is still off.
你觉得怎样? 我们要不要自己打开它?
What do you think? Should we risk opening it without him?
别问我      好吧
Don't ask me.        Yeah, right.
这样吧 我们只把它打开
You know what? We're just gonna open it up,
我不会碰那封信
and I won't touch the letter.
成交      好的
Deal.        Okay.
我们动手吧      好吧
Let's do it.        All right.
你需要帮忙吗?
Do you need help?
不 我觉得我能行
No, I think I'm okay.
哎哟! 该死!
Ow! Damn it!
你没事吧? 怎么了?
Are you okay? What is it?
切到手指了 没事的
Aah. I cut myself. I'll be all right.
没关系的 你准备好了吗?      嗯
It's okay. Are you ready?        Yeah.
好吧      动手吧
Okay.        Let's do it.
动手吧      像这样?
Let's go.        Like this?
是的 有点难开
Yeah. It's a little tough.
好的 打开了
All right. Yeah, there you go.
小心点
Careful.
好的
Yeah.
哇哦
Wow.
仔细看看刀柄
Take a careful look at the hilt.
告诉我你看到了什么      宝石图案
Tell me what you see.        The gemstone settings.
这是中世纪的工艺 不是么?
It's a medieval technique, isn't it?
很好 大约是十三世纪的
Very good. Thirteenth century, most likely.
瞧 有三座雕像
Look. Three statues.
有点吓人      是啊
That's kind of scary.        Yeah.
拿着它      就这样
You take it.        There you go.
好的 里面还有
Okay. Oh, there's more.
看看这个 好的
Look at this. Okay.
保存得真好
They're so well-preserved.
是啊      看看上面的字
Yeah.        Look at this writing.
里面还有      嗯?
Hey, there's more.        Yeah?
这像是某种护身符
This is some kind of talisman.
你能读懂上面的字吗?
Can you read the writing?
不能 现在不行
No, not offhand.
是某种古老的语言
It's some ancient language.
知道么 去取亚兰语和
You know what? Go and grab the Aramaic and
迈锡尼语的词典过来
Mycenaean dictionaries, will you?
好的      他也想让我们马上取得进展
Yeah.        He'll want us to move on this right away.
好的      谢谢
Okay.        Thank you.
不要! 不要!
No! No!
救命啊! 不要!
Help me! No!
母亲 母亲
Mater. Mater.
快走
Go now.
快走!
Go now!
喂 救命! 请帮帮我!
Hello. Help! Please help me!
你看见4个人 按照你的话说
You saw four people, and they were,
他们是"畸形的"?
to use your words, ''deformed''?
我没看清他们的脸 但...
I didn't see their faces, but...
他们的行为方式非常奇怪
there was something very strange about the way they moved.
怎么会?      就像是...
How so?        It was like-
天哪 他们把她撕成了碎片
God, they tore her to bits.
鲜血...      等一等
The blood, it was-        Wait.
他们的行为如何?
How did they move?
他们好像有点驼背
Well, they were sort of hunched over.
但我只看了几秒钟而已
But I only saw them for a few seconds.
就是说有3个畸形的人
So there were three deformed people.
是的 和一只猴子
Yes, and a monkey.
猴子?      是的 它在追赶我
A monkey?        Yes. It was chasing me.
好吧
Okay.
萨拉
Sarah.
你到底在这个机构做什么 萨拉?
So what exactly do you do for the institute, Sarah?
我在研究艺术品修复和考古学
I'm studying art restoration and archaeology.
在这些失窃的艺术品被带走之前...
And did you manage to catalog these pieces of art...
你为它们做登记了吗?      没有
that were stolen before they were taken away?        No.
我们才刚开始检查它们
We were just starting to examine them.
瞧 我把我所知道的都说了
Look, I told you everything I know.
请问我现在可以回家了吗?
Can I please go home now, please?
萨拉!      没关系 让他进来
Sarah!        No, it's okay. Let him in.
迈克尔 我的天哪      萨拉! 你没事吧?
Michael. Oh, my God.        Sarah! Hey, are you okay?
迈克尔 太恐怖了 吉赛尔她...
Michael, it was horrible. And Giselle, she-
没事了 没事了 有我在这儿 没事了
It's okay. It's okay. I'm here now. It's okay.
你好 我是迈克尔・皮尔斯 博物馆的经理
Hi, I'm Michael Pierce. I'm the director of the museum.
我是恩佐・马奇 此次调查组组长
I am Enzo Marchi, the head of this investigation.
很好 瞧 我现在要带她回家 可以吗?
Great. Look, I'm gonna take her home now, okay?
当然可以 没问题
Of course. No problem.
谢谢      你没事吧?
Thank you.        Are you all right?
我简直不敢相信
I can't believe it.
你听到了吗?
Did you hear that?
她疯了
She's crazy.
你是个侦探 知道吗?
You're some detective, you know?
当然      对她留点神
Sure.        Go and keep an eye on her.
我今晚可以住你家吗?
Can I stay at your place tonight?
我真的不想一个人呆着
I really don't feel like being alone.
当然可以
Of course you can.
外面冷死了
It's freezing outside.
我能生火吗?
Can I light a fire?
当然 我过去看看保罗
Yeah, sure. I'm just gonna check on Paul.
好的
All right.
不错 他还在睡觉
Good. Well, he's still asleep.
今晚发生了件很奇怪的事
Something very strange happened to me tonight.
我都有点不好意思告诉你
And, uh, I feel almost embarrassed to tell you about it.
什么?
What?
向我保证你不会觉得我在发疯
Promise me you won't think I'm crazy.
我保证      好的
I promise.        All right.
我被困在了那里
I was trapped in there.
根本不可能活着离开
And there was no way I was gonna get out of there alive.
然后...      怎么了?
And then-        What?
算了 没什么
Nah, never mind.
说呀 告诉我
Come on. Tell me.
然后...
And then...
我听到脑海中有个声音...
I heard a voice in my head...
跟我说快走
telling me to go.
然后 砰的一声 门猛地开了
And then- bam- the doors slammed open!
我是说 他们是锁着的 猛地开了
I mean, they were locked and they slammed open!
我... 还有这个女人...
And I-And there was this woman too-
爸爸?
Dad?
嗨 小老虎! 你起来做什么? 嗯?
Hey, tiger! What are you doing up? Huh?
我还以为你睡着了 过来
I thought you were asleep. Ah, come here.
你好 保罗      你好 萨拉
Hi, Paul.        Hi, Sarah.
你想喝热巧克力吗?
Do you want some hot chocolate?
想喝 我能晚点睡吗?
Yes. Can I stay up late?
能 你可以晚点睡
Yes, you can stay up late.
我们来选本书 然后送你上床睡觉
Let's choose one of your books, and we'll take you to bed.
你想要哪一本? 这本? 好吧
Which one are you gonna get? This one? Okay.
我呆会儿把热巧克力送进来
I'm gonna come in with the hot chocolate now.
快点 快上床
Come on. Back to bed.
马上进来 好吗?
Coming in a second, all right?
我只是想不通
I just can't get my head around it.
他们为什么要杀害吉赛尔?
Why did they have to kill Giselle?
那个骨灰瓮里有什么这么重要?
What was so important about that urn?
根据你所说的 他们可能是护身符
Well, from what you told me, they could be talismans.
听我说 我明天早上去见布鲁斯卡主教
Look, I'm gonna go and see Monsignor Brusca tomorrow morning.
说不定他知道些事情
Maybe he can shed some more light on it.
你是怎么认识他的?
How do you know him?
他几年前曾来伦敦作演讲
Well, he came to London a few years ago
谈论唯心论
to lecture on spiritualism.
他还是神秘主义
And he's meant to be a leading authority
和神秘科学的权威
on mysticism and the occult sciences-
"科学"? 得啦 你才不会相信那些东西
"Sciences''? Come on. You don't believe in that crap.
神秘学?      是啊
The occult?        Yeah.
可能信 也可能不信
Well, maybe, maybe not.
哼      什么?
Hmph.        What?
我只是...
I was just-
什么 你以为这世上
What,you don't think there are forces
没有未知的力量存在?
out there we don't understand?
不会吧 不会 你和我都是科学家
Not really, no. You and I are scientists.
我们应当相信那些看得见摸得着的东西
We're supposed to believe in what we see and what we touch.
巧克力!      看到了吧? 力量
The chocolate!        See? Forces.
我总是听到那声音 在我脑海中回响
I keep hearing that voice echoing in my head.
我觉得我要疯了
I think I'm going crazy.
你不会疯的 过来
You're not going crazy. Come here.
你不是要发疯 你只是
You're not going crazy. You just-
只是需要睡眠
Just need to sleep.
快点睡吧
Just try to sleep, hmm?
混乱 鲜血 泪水
Chaos. Blood. Tears.
母亲! 母亲!
Mater.! Mater.!
宝贝 宝贝
Certo. Certo.
我要杀了你! 我要杀了你!
I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
早上好 神父      早上好
Morning, Father.        Morning.
我来找布鲁斯卡主教
I'm here to see Monsignor Brusca.
你还不知道吧?
Oh, you don't know, do you?
找到棺材的第二天 他就中风了
He had a stroke the day after we found the coffin .
昏迷之前
He was conscious for only a few minutes
只清醒了几分钟
before he slipped into a coma.
深感遗憾
I'm so sorry.
听我说 我知道现在不是时候
Look, I... understand this isn't the best time...
但我真的非常需要知道那个骨灰瓮的情况
but I really do need to know as much as I can about the urn.
喂 听我说 我真的不知道为什么...
Look. Look, I really don't know why...
会有人想要带走那个骨灰瓮
anyone would want to take that urn.
我只知道棺材上
The only thing I know is that there was a name
有个名字 奥斯卡・德拉瓦莱
on the coffin: Oscar de la Valle.
奥斯卡・德拉瓦莱?      是的
Oscar de la Valle?        Yes.
你知道他是谁吗?
Do you know who he was?
主教认为他就是在奥斯塔(意大利城市)...
The monsignor thought it was the same man...
流传了几千年的
who figures in an old story
一个古老传说里的人物
that's been popular in Aosta for centuries.
很多人 也包括我 只当它是神话传说
Most people, including me, consider it nothing but legend.
布鲁斯卡不同 所以他才把
Brusca didn't. That's why he
那些物件寄给你以作查证
sent the items to you for verification.
你能跟我说说那个传说吗?
Well, can you tell me about the story?
在1814年...
In 1814...
工人们翻修奥斯塔的教堂时...
workers renovating the church curia in Aosta...
发现了一个骨灰瓮
discovered an urn.
里面有几样东西
There were several items inside it...
包括一件新教时期的衣服
including a dress that may have been from pagan times.
传说发现骨灰瓮的
As the legend has it, packs of wolves
第二天晚上
came out of the forest...
大批狼群从森林中奔涌而出
the night after the urn was found.
他们把新埋入墓地的尸体挖出来
They dug up freshly-buried bodies in the graveyard...
撕成碎片
and tore them to bits.
当地的牧师决定把骨灰瓮送往梵蒂冈
The local priest decided to send the urn to the Vatican.
奥斯卡・德拉瓦莱自愿运送它
Oscar de la Valle volunteered to deliver it.
他是个贵族出身的骑士
He was a knight of noble birth.
只有他才有资格与教皇说话
Only he was allowed to talk with the pope.
他的旅途很糟糕
He had one bad trip.
他走到哪里 死亡和毁灭就跟到哪里
Wherever he went, death and destruction followed.
孩子死了 庄稼烧了
Children died. Crops burned.
村庄全毁了
Whole villages were devastated.
很多城镇都拒绝让德拉瓦莱通行
Many towns refused to let De la Valle enter.
人们处于恐慌之中
People were in a panic.
抵达维泰博时 他染上重病 眼睛也瞎了
By the time he reached Viterbo, he was both sick and blind.
教堂收留了他
The church took him in.
他六天后去世 可能死于寒热病
He died six days later. Maybe it was malarial fever.
他的尸体被埋葬在一个秘密的地方
His body was buried in a secret place.
骨灰瓮被捆绑在他的棺材上
The urn was chained to his coffin
并用十字架封印
and sealed with crucifixes.
发现骨灰瓮之后
After the urn was found,
主教像是变了一个人
the monsignor was a different person.
他开始胡说八道
He began talking nonsense.
等等 等一等
Wait. Wait, wait.
我...对了
I-Yes-
他中风时正在写这个      这儿
He was writing this when he had the stroke.        Here.
是骨灰瓮内物品的清单
It's a list of what was in the urn.
"眼泪之母"      眼泪之母 对
" Mater Lacrimarum.''        Mater Lacrimarum. Yes.
主教认为骨灰瓮...
The monsignor thought the urn...
和它里面的东西都有魔力...
and its contents were magical...
他们属于一个邪恶的女巫
that they belonged to an evil witch...
叫做眼泪之母 即泪之母
named Mater Lacrimarum- the Mother of Tears.
真是遗憾
It's such a shame.
他是个睿智的人 慈祥...
He was a brilliant man- kind...
还是个极好的老师
and a wonderful teacher.
死时却相信这些无稽之谈...
To end his days believing in this nonsense-
有句话他跟我说过多次 相信跟你也说过
I'm sure he told you the same thing he told me many times-
上帝为我们所做的安排除了他 无人知晓
that God's plans for us are a mystery to everyone but him.
布鲁斯卡主教写下这个是有原因的
Monsignor Brusca wrote this for a reason.
我们可能不能理解 但一定事出有因
One we might not understand, but a reason nonetheless.
再见 神父
Good-bye, Father.
别动 我叫你别动!
Hold still. I said hold still!
不要! 救命啊!
No! Help me!
张开你的腿 张开你的腿!
Open your legs. Open your legs!
不要! 救命啊!
No! Help me!
停下! 不要动!
Stop! Freeze!
别动!
Freeze!
迈克尔?
Michael?
有人吗?
Hello?
有人在家吗?
Is there anybody home?
迈克尔?
Michael?
保罗?
Paul?
迈克尔?
Michael?
迈克尔! 出什么事了?
Michael! What happened?
他们把他带走了
They took him.
谁把他带走了?       保姆...
- Who took him?      - The babysitter...
她说出去两分钟
went out for two minutes, she said.
她回来的时候...
She came back...
发现了这个...
and she found... this-
"如果你想再见你儿子就...
''If you want to see your son again...
保持沉默"
keep the silentium. ''
沉默
The silentium.
迈克尔 我很遗憾
Michael, I'm sorry.
我真的很遗憾 亲爱的
I'm so sorry, darling.
这些符号...与我在骨灰瓮上看到的一样
Those symbols- they are the same ones I saw on the urn.
我知道! 是同一批人 是某种巫术
I know! It's the same people. It's some kind of black magic.
巫术?
Black magic?
我不知道什么巫术...      什么?
I don't know about black magic-        What?
什么 你以为这只是巧合?
What, you think this is all some sort of coincidence?
不 我没这么说...
No, I didn't say-
别这么天真! 吉赛尔死了
Don't be so bloody naive! Giselle's dead.
布鲁斯卡昏迷了 现在他们又带走了保罗
Brusca's in a coma. Now they've taken Paul.
这一切都与骨灰瓮和那些护身符密切相关
It's- It's all connected with the urn and-and those talismans.
而且他们想要我停止调查 要我保持沉默
And they want me to stop looking. They want me to keep quiet.
关于什么? 对什么保持沉默?
About what? Keep quiet about what?
黑暗... 向罗马聚拢 你没看到吗?
The darkness... gathering around Rome. You haven't seen it?
每时每刻都在进行着 跟我来!
It's happening. Here, come with me!
过来 我带你去看 过来      我来了
Look. Let me show you. Look.        I'm coming.
你怎么看待这些? 在哪儿呢?
What do you think all this is? Where is it?
频繁自杀事件 两天内发生52起!      是的
An epidemic of suicides, 52 in two days!        Yes.
看 暴力袭击浪潮充斥整座城市
Look. A wave of violence spreads through the city-
谋杀 纵火 绑架 破坏教堂
murders, fires, kidnappings, church vandalism-
是的 迈克尔 你吓倒我了 我知道这些
Yes, Michael, you're scaring me. I- I know all this.
我要去蒙泰莱奥内(意大利城市)
I'm going to Monteleone.
那儿有个牧师 约翰尼斯神父
There's a priest there, Father Johannes.
他到底能做什么 来挽回这个局面?
And what on earth could he do to help this situation?
他是法师 梵蒂冈认证的最后的法师之一
He's an exorcist- one of the last confirmed by the Vatican.
他比我所认识的任何人都更了解神秘学
He knows more about the occult than anyone else I know.
他能够帮我神不知鬼不觉地
And he'll be able to help me get Paul back
把保罗带回来
in a way they can't detect.
听我说 迈克尔 为什么不找警察呢?
Look, Michael, why don't we try the police?
不! 不要警察!
No! No police!
在博物馆你也见识了他们看你的眼神
You saw the way they looked at you at the museum.
以为你根本就是疯了
They thought you were fucking crazy!
迈克尔 听着 我爱保罗 和你一样爱他...
Michael, look, I-I love Paul, okay, as much as you do...
但我认为这不是最好的方法
but I don't know if this is the best way-
他是我的儿子!
He is my son!
不是你的!
Not yours!
迈克尔
Michael.
见鬼! 小心点 见鬼!
Damn it! Be careful, damn it!
下地狱吧
You rot in hell.
你们准备好庆祝了吗?      当然!
Are you ready for the celebration?        Of course!
打扰一下
Excuse me.
复仇三女神
Three Furies.
复仇女神
Furies.
命运三女神
Three Fates.
优雅三女神
Three Graces.
黛安娜 三头人...
Diana, the three-headed-
三神一体
The Triad.
为什么总是三个?
Why are they always three?
抱歉 喂?
Sorry. Hello?
萨拉 嗨 是我 迈克尔      迈克尔?
Sarah, hi. It's me. It's Michael.        Michael?
你在哪儿?
Where are you?
等一下 不 不 等等 听我说
Wait, no, no. Wait, wait, listen.
我真的需要你的帮助
I-I really need your help, okay?
我当然会帮你
Yeah, of course I'll help you.
告诉我该怎么做
Just tell me what to do.
你必须...      迈克尔?
No, you've got-        Michael?
迈克尔!
Michael!
喂 你还在吗? 迈克尔!
Hello, are you there? Michael!
救我 萨拉 救我
Help me, Sarah. Help me.
迈克尔 你还在吗?
Michael, are you still there?
迈克尔? 迈克尔!
Michael? Michael!
嗨 姐妹们
Hey, sister.
等一等!
Chotomateh!
西蒙尼 埃克!
Simone. Ikeh!
好的 加油 找到她
Okay, please, come on. Let's find her.
同时 请保持低调 可以吗?
And try not to draw too much attention to yourselves, okay?
好的 我知道 我知道
Okay, I know, I know.
好的 你们俩跟我走
Okay, you two with me. Come on. This way.
行动! 行动!
Move! Move!
大家 我们是警察
People, we're the police.
不 不 不 你不能进去 不能进去
No, no, no,you can't go in. Can't go in.
小姐 你也是 请往前走 谢谢 往前走
Lady, you too. Move on, please. Thank you. Move on.
集中精神      嗯?
Concentrate.        Huh?
集中精神!
Concentrate!
他们看不见你!
They won't see you.!
别担心 他们看不见你!
Don't worry. They won't see you.!
跟丢了
We lost her.
好的
Okay.
干什么?
What?
打扰一下 这列火车往哪儿开?
Excuse me. Where's this train going?
前往渥特 30分钟后出发      谢谢
Orte. Leaves in 30 minutes.        Thank you.
迈克尔?      这是
Michael?        This is
迈克尔・皮尔斯的语音信箱
Michael Pierce's voicemail.
哔声之后请留言
Please leave a message after the tone.
迈克尔 我遇到麻烦了 现在去蒙泰莱奥内
Michael, I've run into problems. I'm going to Monteleone.
再见
Bye.
需要帮忙吗?
Can I help you?
对不起 我听不懂
Sorry, I don't understand.
走开!
Get out!
去蒙泰莱奥内的火车 将从9号轨道出发
The train for Monteleone now leaving on track nine.
她到底在哪里?      可能在里面
Where the fuck is she?        Maybe in there.
她可能在里面!
Maybe she's in there!
萨拉・曼蒂杀了这个女人 因为她看见...
Well, Sarah Mandy killed this woman because she saw...
曼蒂小姐在那里袭击了达席尔瓦
Miss Mandy attacking Da Silva over there.
就这么简单
As simple as that.
曼蒂最多只有110磅(50公斤)?
Mandy weighs 1 1 0 pounds, at the most?
达席尔瓦 愿他安息 是个大男人
Da Silva, God rest his soul, was a fucking gorilla.
而且还携有武器
And he was armed.
不 这个案子比我们想象的要复杂
No, there's more to this case than we think.
请把他们的尸体运回去
Can you move them back, please?
不要! 不要! 不要!
Nafech.! Nafech.! Nafech.!
不要! 不要! 不要! 不要!
Nafech! Nafech! Nafech! Nafech!
不要! 不要!
Nafech.! Nafech.!
Nafech! Nafech!
不要! 不要!
Nafech.! Nafech.!
谁呀?      你好?
Yes?        Hello?
我叫萨拉・曼蒂 我来找
My name is Sarah Mandy. I'm looking for
我一个朋友 迈克尔・皮尔斯
a friend of mine, Michael Pierce.
他来找约翰内斯神父
He came to see Father Johannes.
不 对不起 他不在这里
No, I'm sorry, he's not here.
什么?
What?
那我能见约翰内斯神父吗?
Could I see FatherJohannes then?
我有很重要的事
It's very important.
你明天再来吧
You have to come back tomorrow.
他今天不能见你
He can't see you today.
对不起 但这样不行
I'm sorry, but that's not possible.
请你告诉他 我不会占用他太多时间
Please, tell him I won't take much of his time.
拜托了
Please.
好吧 进来吧
All right. Come in.
谢谢 非常感谢
Thanks. Thanks a lot.
你看起来刚经历一场艰苦的旅程
You look like you had a hard trip.
你拥有它 你知道的
You have it, you know.
你母亲的凝视
Your mother's gaze.
你是埃莉莎・曼蒂的女儿 是吗?
You're Elisa Mandy's daughter, aren't you?
我是玛塔・克鲁西
I'm Marta Colussi.
你长得真像她
You really look just like her.
很多年前在德国 我就认识你母亲了
I knew your mother many years ago in Germany.
她是个极好的老师
She was a wonderful teacher.
我向她学习了很多
I learned so much from her.
她是我认识的最厉害的女巫
She was a great spiritualist- the best I've ever known.
我母亲是一位舞者      还是个医师
My mother was a dancer.        And a healer.
白女巫 这样说你也许更能接受
A white witch, if you will.
我觉得你继承了她的天赋
And it seems to me you've inherited some of her gifts.
听我说 小姐      叫我玛塔
Listen, lady-        It's Marta.
玛塔 不管你是谁...
Marta. Whoever you are...
我不认识你 也不是来找你的
I don't know you and I didn't come here to talk to you.
请你不要烦我 可以吗?
Please leave me alone now, okay?
你是怎么从火车站逃出来的?
How did you get away at the train station?
你是谁?
What the-Who are you?
埃莉莎在帮助你 教导你 是不是?
Elisa was helping you. Coaching you, wasn't she?
我... 我不知道
I- I don't know.
我听到... 我听到一个声音
I heard- I heard a voice.
你真的认识我母亲?      非常熟悉
Did you really know my mother?        Quite well.
你并不了解她 是吗?      不了解
You don't know much about her, do you?        No.
我对我的父母没有多大印象
I don't remember much about my parents.
他们意外去世的时候我还小
I was very young when they died in the accident.
在弗莱堡(位于德国)出了车祸
The car crash in Freiburg.
不 亲爱的 我很遗憾 那不是真的
No, honey. I'm sorry. That's not what happened.
你的父母是被谋杀的
Your parents were murdered.
什么? 你在说什么?
What? What are you talking about?
从没有人告诉我
Nobody ever told me this.
你在说什么?
What are you saying?
你母亲勇于和一个极其强大的黑女巫对抗
Your mother dared to fight a very powerful black witch:
叹息之母
Mater Suspiriorum, the Mother of Sighs.
The Mother of Sighs.
约翰内斯神父
FatherJohannes.
多少滴?      20 谢了
How many drops?        Twenty, please.
你看起来疲倦极了 你需要休息
You look exhausted. You need to rest.
外面发生这么多事情 我必须战斗
With everything that's going on now? I have to fight.
我必须战斗
I have to fight!
请保持冷静 先喝药
Stay calm now. Please. Take your drops.
你的弱点也正是你的长处 神父
Your weakness is your strength, Father.
我知道你要来
I've been expecting you.
你是萨拉      是的
You're Sarah.        Yes.
你好
Hi.
我有很多事要告诉你 关于你的母亲...
There's a lot I have to tell you-about your mother...
关于你 以及这个...
about you, and about a world-
你几乎不认识的世界
you hardly know.
一千多年以前...
More than a thousand years ago...
三姐妹在黑海海岸...
witchcraft was birthed...
创立了巫术
by the shores of the Black Sea by three sisters.
多年来 她们漫游世界...
For years they roamed the earth...
走到哪里就把死亡和毁灭带到哪里
bringing death and destruction wherever they went.
翻开任何一本艺术史
Search any art history book
你都能找到她们的图片
and you'll find images of them.
最终他们找到了归宿
Eventually, they found homes.
叹息之母定居弗莱堡
Mater Suspiriorum, the Mother of Sighs, settled in Freiburg.
痛苦之母去了纽约
The Mother of Pain, Mater Tenebrarum, went to New York.
眼泪之母来到了罗马
Mater Lacrimarum came to Rome.
她也叫做泪之母
She's known as the Mother of Tears.
她是三姐妹中最残忍也最漂亮的
She's the most cruel and beautiful of the three.
同时还是唯一一个存活的
And she's the only one still alive.
痛苦之母和叹息之母...
Mater Tenebrarum and Mater Suspiriorum...
在很多年前死了
died many years ago.
叹息之母 她杀害了我的父母
The Mother of Sighs. She murdered my parents.
是的 但是在那之前你母亲
Yes. But not before your mother...
将她击成重伤
had injured her horribly.
与你母亲激战后
After fighting your mother,
她被打回了原形
she was reduced to a shell of her former self.
一个叫做苏西・拜伦的年轻舞者...
A young dancer named Suzy Bannion...
终于杀死了她
finally managed to kill her.
但那都是历史
But that's all history.
当布鲁斯卡发现的骨灰瓮开启时...
When that urn Brusca found was opened...
它使泪之母的力量复原了
it restored the Mother ofTears's powers.
你是怎么知道的?
How do you know about that?
你的朋友 迈克尔 告诉我的...
Your friend, Michael, told me about it...
他打电话给我 说到
when he phoned and
一件有魔力的红色短上衣...
spoke of a magic red tunic...
那是一件力量强大的护身符
that would be a great and powerful talisman.
我有预感 女巫们正从...
I've had visions. Witches are coming...
世界各地汇聚过来 庆祝她的归来
from all over the world to celebrate her return.
是的 每天都有人抵达罗马
Yes. They're arriving in Rome every day.
每架飞机 每辆汽车...
Every jet, every car...
每列火车 都带来更多的人
every train brings more.
他们想让罗马再次沦陷...
They aim to make Rome fall again...
从而开启第二个女巫时代
to usher in the Second Age of Witches.
我受不了了 我觉得我要疯了
I can't take it anymore. I feel like I'm going crazy.
你的精神没有问题 萨拉
There's nothing wrong with your mind, Sarah.
疯了的是这个世界
It's the world that's gone crazy.
看一看
Have a look.
看这个
Look at this.
平常我一个月才接到一个驱邪请求...
Usually I have one exorcism request a month...
但在过去几天里
but the last few days,
我接到的案例比这辈子接到的还多
I've had more cases than I've had in my whole life.
每个神父都面临着同样的挑战
Every priest I talk to is faced with the same challenge.
为什么会发生这些事?
Why is all this happening?
泪之母把邪恶散布到各个角落
The Mother ofTears spreads evil wherever she can.
杀害一部分 逼疯一部分
Some she kills, others she drives mad.
她沉迷于混乱与绝望
She revels in chaos and human despair.
我们有工作要做
We have work to do.
我的书房里有本书 能够指引我们
I have a book in my study that shows us the way.
瓦莱里娅! 瓦莱里娅!
Valeria! Valeria!
瓦莱里娅
Valeria.
愿死者安息!
Requiescat!
约翰内斯神父!
Father Johannes!
母亲?      玛塔 回来! 回来!
Mother?        Marta, come back! Come back!
母亲 我服从你!
Mother, I obeyed you!
快点 我们走吧!
Come on, let's go!
让我... 来人哪...
Let me- Somebody help-
玛塔! 玛塔 救我!
Marta! Marta, help me!
我的天哪!
Oh, my God!
玛塔! 玛塔 走吧!
Marta! Marta, let's go!
你的车在哪?      就在这儿
Where's your car?        It's right there.
他们来了 天哪 快跑!
They're coming! Oh, God, run!
锁了! 开门 开门!
It's locked! Open- Open up!
快开门!      我找不到钥匙了!
Open it!        I can't find my key!
他们为何要追逐我?
Why were they all after me?
你的母亲
Your mother.
你在干什么?      打电话给迈克尔
What are you doing?        I'm calling Michael.
你疯了吗? 他们能利用信号追踪你
Are you crazy? They can trace you with it.
你说得对 扔了它
You're right. Fuck it.
今晚来我家睡吧 安全一点
Come to my place tonight. It'll be safer for you.
不 我想要回家
No, I'd rather go home.
迈克尔可以去那儿找我
Michael can reach me there.
这是我的电话号码和地址
Here's my phone number and address.
任何时候打给我都可以      谢谢
Call me anytime. It's no bother.        Thank you.
你是埃莉莎的女儿 这比家人还亲
You're Elisa's daughter. That's closer than family.
我并不想吓唬你 但是...
I don't mean to scare you, but...
他们知道你是谁 萨拉
they know who you are, Sarah.
向我保证你不会相信任何人
Promise me you won't trust anyone.
我保证
I promise.
发生什么事了?
What's going on here?
他们在焚烧教堂
They are burning the churches.
情况越来越糟
It's getting worse.
母亲! 母亲!
Mater! Mater!
我的公寓里有人!
There was somebody at my apartment.!
我从门缝中看到了灯光还有影子
I saw lights and shadows under the door.
我觉得我要疯了
I feel like I'm going crazy!
天哪! 救我 请救救我! 请救救我!
God! Help. Please help me. Help me, please.
深呼吸
Take a deep breath.
谢谢你      冷静下来
Thank you.        Calm down.
进来
Come in.
埃尔加 这是萨拉      你好
Elga, meet Sarah.        Hi.
她在这里做什么?      没事的
What is she doing here?        It's okay.
玛塔 你必须帮帮我
Marta, you have to help me.
我不知道自己出什么事了
I don't know what's happening to me.
跟我来      你必须向我解释
Come with me.        You have to explain.
为什么有这么多事发生在我身上 为什么?
Why is all this happening to me? Why?
他们知道你是谁 他们不会冒险的
They know who you are. They can't take any chances.
但我 我 我什么都不知道
But I- I- I don't know anything.
你比自己想象的知道更多
You know more than you think you do.
不然有这么多怪物追逐你
How else have you survived this long
你如何能活到现在?
with those monsters after you?
埃尔加 能让我们单独呆会儿吗?
Elga, would you please excuse us for a minute?
拜托 求你了
Oh, please. Come on.
拜托?
Please?
你有天赋 萨拉
You have gifts, Sarah.
如果你想活下去 就必须接受现实
You need to accept that if you want to survive.
好好看
Watch and learn.
飘荡的灵魂
Drifting spirits.
他们无处不在 罗马尤其多
They are everywhere, especially here in Rome.
老房子里到处都是鬼魂
The old houses are full of ghosts.
想一想
Think about it.
罗马城有2700年的历史...
The city is 27 00 years old...
我们正站在五层坟墓之上
and we are standing on five layers of graves.
你怎么做的?      你也可以做到
How do you do it?        You can do it too.
运用你的天赋 就可以见人所未见
With your gifts, you can see what others can't.
闭上眼睛
Close your eyes.
聚集你所有能量...
Focus all of your energy...
集中在这一点上
and concentrate on this spot.
很好
Good.
现在像我做的那样 轻吹一口气
Now just do like I did and blow.
萨拉
Sarah.
不 不可能啊
No, it can't be.
妈咪?
Mommy?
萨拉
Sarah.
妈咪!      不要碰她 不然她会消失的
Mommy!        You can't touch her or she'll disappear.
别管我
Leave me alone.
泪之母越来越强大 越来越强 萨拉!
Mater Lacrimarum grows stronger. She grows stronger, Sarah!
你在哪儿啊?
Where-Where are you?
妈咪! 妈咪!
Mommy! Mommy!
你的处境很危险 亲爱的孩子
You're in great danger, my dear child.
学会战斗      不要!
Learn to fight.        No.!
不要! 不要!
No! No!
别走 妈咪! 请不要离开我 妈咪 求你!
Don't go, Mommy.! Don't leave me.! Mommy, please.!
妈咪!
Mommy!
请把她带回来 求你!
Please make her come back. Please!
妈...
Mo-
不要离开我 不要走
Don't leave me. Don't leave.
她让我战斗
She told me to fight.
你一定要帮助我 我必须战斗 求你
You have to help me. I have to fight. Please.
我只是个巫女
I'm only a psychic.
我能与灵魂交流 仅此而已
I can communicate with spirits, but that's about it.
我没有你母亲的天赋 也没有你的
I don't have your mother's gifts, or yours.
你需要人指引你
You need someone who can guide you,
为你指出正确的方向
point you in the right direction.
是的
Yes.
明天我会把你介绍给古格列尔莫・德威特
Tomorrow I'll introduce you to Guglielmo de Witt.
他是个伟大的比利时思想家      好的
He's a great Belgian thinker.        Okay.
他会告诉你些有用的信息 但愿不会太迟
He'll tell you something useful, if it's not too late.
谢谢你
Thank you.
不 不
No. No.
快接电话
Pick up the phone.
快点 玛塔 快接电话!
Come on, Marta, pick up the phone!
喂? 喂 玛塔?
Hello? Hello, Marta?
玛塔 你必须马上离开那里
Marta, you have to get out of there now!
玛塔? 喂? 谁在听?
Marta? Hello? Who's there?
快跑! 太晚了!
Run! It's too late!
现在! 快跑!
Now! Run now!
不! 她什么都不知道!
No.! She doesn't know anything.!
不! 不要啊! 不要!
No! Don't do it! Don't do it!
母亲! 母亲!
Mater! Mater!
萨拉在哪儿?
Where is Sarah?
她不在这儿
She isn't here.
笨蛋!
Idiot!
是你
It is you.
是的
It is.
别倒下 别倒下!
Stay strong. Stay strong.!
妈妈      别倒下 萨拉!
Mom.        Stay strong, Sarah!
好的
Yes.
妈妈 他们对你和爸爸做了什么...
Mom, what did they do to you and Dad when-
事情已经过去了
It's all in the past.
你什么也改变不了 注定要这样的
There's nothing you can do. It was meant to be.
你离开我时 我是那么沮丧 那么生气
I was so upset, so angry at you for leaving me.
请你不要再次抛弃我
Plea- Please don't abandon me again.
原谅我 小萨拉
Forgive me, little Sarah.
我不能再说了
I can't speak anymore.
我现在属于另一个地方 使用你的天赋
I belong to another place now. Use your gifts.
使用它们 使用它们
Use them. Use them.
妈咪
Mommy.
好的 伙计们 听好了
Okay, guys, listen up.
我们要找一个约28岁的女孩
We're looking for a girl around 28.
她的名字叫萨拉・曼蒂
Her name is Sarah Mandy.
如果你看到了 不要接近她
If you see her, don't approach her.
迈克尔?
Michael?
迈克尔 迈...
Michael. Mi-
迈克尔! 迈克尔!
Michael! Michael!
迈克尔 停下!
Michael, stop!
迈克尔?
Michael?
迈克尔
Michael.
你没事吧?
Are you okay?
迈克尔 你生病了
Michael, you're sick.
保罗在哪儿?
Where's Paul?
我还以为...
I thought-
你有没有...
Did you-
我想...
I think-
我想他... 我想他死了
I think he's- I think he's dead.
我的天哪      他们杀了他
Oh, my God.        They killed him.
我的天哪      而我却不能...
Oh, my God.        And I can't-
我现在不想说这件事
I don't want to talk about that now.
我们走吧
Let's go.
我的公寓不安全
My apartment is not safe.
不管我走到哪里 他们...
Everywhere I go, they-
我们去我家
We'll go to my place.
他们不会上那儿找你
They won't look for you there.
不 不 不要开灯
No, no. No lights.
为什么?
Why?
你不想被他们看到吧
We don't want them to see us.
我真高兴 我们找到了彼此
I'm so happy we found each other.
你没事吧?
Are you okay?
你要不休息一下 把外套脱了
Why don't you just rest, take off your coat-
不 不 不
No, no, no.
我太冷了 对不起 我太冷了
I'm freezing. Sorry. I'm freezing.
我连一晚都没有在房子里呆过
I just haven't spent a- a single night inside.
我把每个地方都找遍了
I looked everywhere for him.
发生什么事了?
Yeah, what happened?
因为我去蒙特里尼
Because I went to Monteleone
找你了      我没去成
to find you.        I couldn't get there.
他们在跟踪我
They were following me.
你想告诉我的所有事 我现在都明白了
Everything you were trying to tell me I understand now.
对不起 我以前不相信你
I'm sorry I didn't believe you.
真的很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
好吧
Okay.
你可能不该吸烟
Maybe you shouldn't smoke.
你为什么不...
Why don't you-
你想要我做点什么吗? 喝点茶怎么样?
Do you want me to fix something? Tea, maybe?
不要
No.
不 我... 我没事
No, I'm f- I'm fine.
我只是
I'm just-
我只是太开心了 又找到你了
I'm just pleased I found you again.
我没事 别担心 没事的
I'm fine. Don't worry. Fine.
迈克尔 你在流血!
Michael,you're bleeding.!
没事的      迈克尔 你受伤了!
It's nothing.        Michael,you're hurt.!
不 没关系的
No, it's- it's okay.
没事的
It's nothing.
你说什么 没事? 你受伤了!
What do you mean, it's nothing? You're hurt!
跟你说了没事! 走开!
I told you it's nothing! Get off me!
我说了 滚开!
I told you to get the fuck off me!
你以为他们会放过 我和我的孩子吗?
Do you think they would spare me and my child?
你太天真了
You're so naive.
你逃不掉的
You can't escape her.
但他们杀了你的儿子!
But they killed your son!
你的母亲再也不能帮你了
Your mother can't help you anymore.
我们现在拥有同一个母亲
We all have one mother now.
泪之母
The Mother of Tears.
你这个笨蛋...
You bitch! Oh, you crazy-
你这个疯婆子
you crazy bitch.!
古格里尔莫 玛塔给你的那个名字
Guglielmo. The name Marta gave you.
去找他
Find him.
妈咪!
Mommy!
萨拉!
Sarah!
欢迎收看早间新闻
Welcome back to the morning news.
现在是今日焦点
And now for today's top story.
他们称其为 罗马的再次沦陷
They're calling it the second fall of Rome.
过去几天以来 罗马城
Over the past few days the city has
出现了上百起暴力事件
witnessed hundreds of acts of violence.
马奇侦探 你说他们都是相互关联的?
Detective Marchi, you say that they are all connected?
对
Uh, yes.
都是从罗马艺术博物馆的案件开始的
Everything started with events at the Art Museum of Rome.
即助理馆长吉赛尔・梅尔斯的残忍谋杀案
The brutal murder of the assistant curator, Giselle Mares.
但他们是怎么联系在一起的?
But how does that all tie together?
它是现在发生的所有事件的导火索
It was the trigger for everything that's happening now.
我们呼吁每个人都
We ask everybody to be on the lookout
寻找这个女孩 萨拉・曼蒂...
for this girl, Sarah Mandy...
博物馆惨案的唯一目击证人
the only witness to events at the museum.
如果你见到她...      她是嫌疑人吗?
If you see her-        Is she a suspect?
要是看到她了 请不要接近她
If you see her, do not approach her.
打电话到警局 告知重案组
Call the police and ask to speak to Homicide.
见鬼!
Shit!
混蛋!      不 你才混蛋呢!
Fuck you.!        Oh, no, fuck you.!
把钱还给我!      你在说什么?
Give me my money.!        What are you talking about?
把你的车给我 把你的车给我!
Give me your car. Give me your car!
墨镜!
Sunglasses!
不! 不! 不!
No! No! No!
喂?
Hello?
对 能给我古格里尔莫・德威特的地址吗?
Yes, can I please have the address for Mr. Guglielmo de Witt?
D E W I-两个T
D-E-W-I-double T.
什么事?      我要见古格里尔莫・德威特
Yes?        I need to see Guglielmo de Witt.
你是?
And you are?
他不认识我
My name won't mean anything to him.
好吧 请进
All right. Come in.
你想要见我?
So, you wanted to see me?
请坐
Please sit down.
你也看到了 我行动不方便
As you can see, I- I'm not very mobile.
我来这里是因为我要问你...
I'm here because I- I have to ask you about-
我们炼金术士确实修习古老的艺术...
We alchemists may practice an ancient art...
但我们也看新闻
but we do watch the news.
你以为我会不知道你是谁吗 萨拉・曼蒂?
Do you think I wouldn't know who you are, Sarah Mandy?
警察正到处找你
And that the police is looking for you
因为你犯了谋杀罪
because you're wanted for murder?
关于我们炼金术士的另一件事...
Another thing about us alchemists-
我们并没有好坏之别
we're not all one thing or another.
总之 魔法是好的 巫术...
After all, good magic is good, and black magic is-
也是好的
Well, it's good too.
我们研究巫术 科学...
Some of what we do is magic, science...
神秘学 神智学 自然法则
esoterism, theosophy, natural law.
每一样都会一点
A little of this and a little of that.
这能告诉我你到底是谁...
This will let me know who you really are...
你到底见到过什么
and what you've really seen.
有意思
Interesting.
我看见你有潜在的能力
I see you have latent powers.
主要是本能
Instinct more than anything else.
我看到是玛塔・克鲁西让你过来的
Marta Colussi sent you, I see.
还有你母亲 埃莉莎・曼蒂
So did your mother, Elisa Mandy.
你对我做了什么?
What did you do to me?
你以为我连你是谁都不弄清楚
Did you expect me to just let you waltz in here
就让你大摇大摆走进来?
without making sure who you are?
现在 你到底为何来找我?
Now, why exactly did you come here?
我要找泪之母
I need to find the Mother ofTears.
为什么?      看看这座城市发生了什么
Why?        Look what's happening to the city.
罗马就要崩溃了 必须阻止她
Rome is falling apart. She has to be stopped.
你认为自己能做什么? 杀了她?
What do you think you can do? Kill her?
嗯 我母亲非常强大...
Well, my mother was very powerful...
我想我可能继承了她的天赋
and I think I might have the same gifts.
你什么时候发现的? 昨天?
Which you found out about when? Yesterday?
我不知道
I don't know.
一定有人能够制止这一切
There's got to be some people that can help,
像我母亲这样的人
people like my mother.
约翰内斯神父说...
Father Johannes said that-
眼泪之母将带来
that Mater Lacrimarum is bringing
第二个女巫时代
on the Second Age of Witches.
约翰内斯神父说对了
Father Johannes was right.
这座城市的某个地方已经开始举行庆典了
Somewhere in the city the celebration has already begun.
但恐怕没有什么白女巫
But I'm afraid there is no army of good witches
可以拯救这座城市
out there to come to the rescue.
如果你想要制止她 就必须独自行动
If you want to stop her, you have to do it yourself.
那么我现在是独自一人?
So I'm on my own now?
我又没说不帮忙
I didn't say I wouldn't help.
我不能给你答案 但我可以提供信息
I can't give you answers, but I can share information.
跟我来
Follow me.
几个世纪前 有个叫做维拉里的
Centuries ago, a great Roman
伟大的罗马炼金术士...
alchemist named Varelli...
在这所房子住过一段时间
lived for a time in this villa.
他还是个有才华的建筑师
He was also a gifted architect.
在他生命结束之时
And near the end of his life,
他为那三位母亲建造了住所
he built the residences for the Three Mothers.
这或许能为你提供一点信息
This may tell you something you need to know.
三位母亲
The Three Mothers.
我不知道我要付出怎样的代价...
I don't know how much it will cost me...
因打破炼金术士所称作的"沉默"
to break what we alchemists have always called SI LENTI UM.
我见到了那三位母亲...
I met the three Mothers...
为他们建造了三所房子
and built three houses for them:
一所位于弗莱堡 一所位于纽约...
one in Freiburg, one in New York...
一所位于罗马
and one in Rome.
我发现这些房子里
I discovered too late that
藏有肮脏的秘密时 已经太迟了
these houses hide obscene secrets.
那些姐妹就是从这里...
It is from here that the sisters spread pain...
向全世界散播苦难 泪水和黑暗
tears and darkness throughout the world.
这应该是维拉里在罗马建造的那所房子
This building should be the one Varelli built in Rome.
"你看到的
''What you see...
"并不存在
''does not exist...
"你看不到的才是真实"
and what you cannot see is truth. ''
是个谜语
It's a riddle.
找到眼泪之母的住所...
Find where Mater Lacrimarum resides...
你就找到了谜底
and you'll find the answer.
你真的要这么做?
Are you sure you want to do this?
我还有选择吗?
Do I have a choice?
母亲
Mater.
停车 就停在这里!
Stop. Stop right here!
嗨! 你是谁?
Hey! Who are you?
我 我刚看见几个女人走进来
I, uh- I just saw some women come in.
你看到她们了吗?      没有
Did you see them?        No.
你想向我打听事情?      是的
You here to interview me?        Yeah.
给你
Here.
你在这里住了多久?
How long you've been living here?
很久了
A long time.
三四十年了
Thirty, forty years.
从纳粹在二战末逃走开始
Since the Nazis escaped at the end of the war.
你来之前 谁住在这里?
And who used to live here before you?
我不知道 某个协会
Oh, I don't know. A kind of association.
哲学家 抑或是艺术家 不记得了
Philosophers. Artists maybe. I don't remember.
他们为什么离开?
Why did they leave?
可能因为纳粹占据了这所房子...
Maybe because when the Nazis occupied the villa...
她们折磨并杀害了这里很多人
they tortured and killed a lot of people down here.
嘿! 你不会揭发我吧?
Hey.! You won't report me, will ya?
嘘 嘘
Shh, shh.
放松点
Easy.
她去哪儿了?      我想她走了
Where did she go?        I think she's gone.
我去楼上看看
I'll check upstairs.
呆在这里      好的
Stay here.        Yeah.
她不在那里!      那么她走了 一切正常
She's not there!        Then she's gone. Everything's okay.
你忘了我们该做什么了 是不是?
You forgot what we were supposed to do, didn't you?
没有      没有?
No.        No?
只要有人过来四下张望 就告诉他们!
Inform them every time somebody comes to look around!
你懂吗?      懂!
Understand?        Yes!
懂!      走吧!
Yes.        Move!
他们去哪儿了? 他们...      嘘
Where did they go? They just-        Shh.
"他们在这里 我能感觉到
They're in here. I can feel it.
"你看到的并不存在..."
''What you see does not exist...
你看不到的才是真实"
and what you cannot see is truth. ''
这所房子的秘密
The secret of the house.
那些符号与我在骨灰瓮上看到的符号一样
Those are the same symbols I saw on the urn.
地下墓穴
Catacombs.
这些是未发掘的地下墓穴
These are unexplored catacombs.
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
这是泪之母
This is the home of the Mother of Tears...
和她的追随者的家
and her followers.
我的天哪
Dear God.
女巫
Witches.
女巫?
Witches?
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
你会知道的
You'll see.
站在我身后
Stay behind me.
优雅三女神
The three Graces.
你在这里做什么?
What are you doing down here?
我是个艺术史学家 我只是想看看...
I'm an art historian. I just wanted to see-
跟我们走 我带你去看
Come with us. I'll let you see something.
我们会给你看的 是的! 我们会给你看的!
We'll show you! Yeah! We'll show you!
快点!
Come on.!
母亲 给我们力量!
Mother, give us power.!
全烧了!
Burn it all!
我会的! 我会的!
I will! I will!
我会的!
I will.!
母亲! 母亲!
Mater! Mater!
母亲!      母亲!
Mater.!        Mater.!
看哪 母亲 一个擅闯者!
Look, Mother! An intruder!
等等!
Wait!
拿下他!
Get him!
我们要生吃了你!
We'll eat you alive!
绞死他!
Hang him!
我们的时代...
Our hour...
即将到来!
is coming!
你好 萨拉
Hello, Sarah.
过来
Come here.
谁想吃这个女孩?
Who wants to eat the girl?
我
Me.
我们已经为这一刻...
We have waited for this moment...
等了一千年了!
for one thousand years.!
我们的力量已经恢复!
Our power is here.!
现在没有人可以阻止我们!
No one can stop us now.!
没有人!
No one!
不要!
No!
该死的!      地震了!
Damn you.!        It's an earthquake.!
不!
No!
萨拉!
Sarah.!
嘘 嘘 是我! 是我! 是我! 是我!
Shh! Shh! It's me, it's me! It's me! It's me!
没事了 没事了 没事了
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
恩佐 恩佐!
Enzo. Enzo!
快走 快走! 快走!
Go. Go! Go!
母亲
Mother.
~ 母亲 ~
~ Mater~
~ 眼泪 ~
~ Lacrimarum ~
~ 眼泪之母 ~
~ Mater Lacrimarum ~
~ 向怪癖女王致敬 ~
~ Hail to the queen of rare delights ~
~ 邪恶和悲剧是她巫术的琴弦 ~
~ Malefic and tragic are the strings of her magic ~
~ 彻夜尖叫 ~
~ Screaming through the night ~
~ 她是性欲 是死亡 或更甚 ~
~ She is sex and death and more ~
~ 繁华城市内邪恶的香味 ~
~ The scent of evil in the glittering city ~
~ 是处女 又是荡妇 ~
~ A virgin and a whore ~
~ 亵渎神明的号角声 ~
~ For the horns of blasphemy ~
~ 母亲 ~
~ Mater~
~ 她是我们的泪之母 ~
~ She's our Mother of Tears ~
~ 眼泪 ~
~ Lacrimarum ~
~ 风声咆哮 ~
~ The howling on the wind ~
~ 母亲 ~
~ Mater~
~ 她沉湎于我们所有的恐惧 ~
~ She's the lover of all our fears ~
~ 眼泪 ~
~ Lacrimarum ~
~ 母亲 ~
~ Mater~
~ 眼泪 ~
~ Lacrimarum ~
~ 母亲 ~
~ Mater~
~ 向风暴女神问好 ~
~ Hail to the goddess of the storm ~
~ 在一束光线的深渊中起舞 ~
~ Dancing on the abyss in a blaze of light ~
~ 暗星重生 ~
~ A darkened star reborn ~
~ 当月亮高悬夜空 ~
~ When the moon hangs in the sky ~
~ 静谧 比血色落日更加浓厚 ~
~ Sabbatical and fatter than the blood red sunset ~
~ 可知道原因 ~
~ Know the reason why ~
~ 今日天堂起火 ~
~ The heavens burned today ~
~ 母亲 ~
~ Mater~
~ 她是我们的泪之母 ~
~ She's our Mother of Tears ~
~ 眼泪 ~
~ Lacrimarum ~
~ 母亲 ~
~ Mater~
~ 她是我们的泪之母 ~
~ She's our Mother of Tears ~
~ 眼泪 ~
~ Lacrimarum ~
~ 母亲 ~
~ Mater~
~ 她是我们的泪之母 ~
~ She's our Mother of Tears ~
~ 眼泪 ~
~ Lacrimarum ~
~ 风声咆哮 ~
~ The howling on the wind ~
~ 母亲 ~
~ Mater~
~ 她是我们的泪之母 ~
~ She's our Mother of Tears ~
~ 眼泪 ~
~ Lacrimarum ~
~ 人类罪恶愈深 ~
~ The more in mortal sin ~
~ 母亲 ~
~ Mater~
~ 她是我们的泪之母 ~
~ She's our Mother of Tears ~
~ 眼泪 ~
~ Lacrimarum ~
~ 宇宙混乱 ~
~ Chaos in the cosmos ~
~ 母亲 ~
~ Mater~
~ 她沉湎于我们所有的恐惧 ~
~ She's the lover of all our fears ~
~ 眼泪 ~
~ Lacrimarum ~
~ 母亲 ~
~ Mater~
~ 眼泪 ~
~ Lacrimarum ~
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入